Chen Zhou you just got back
Did the chairman arrange for you
to get familiar with the group's business first
Yes
Fu's has many project lines
Unlike those outside local risk meetings
where you can judge by reading a few contracts
I heard Mrs Fu was also involved
in the Chengxi Yunwan project
Involved in the risk review
But the Su family's projects and
Fu's are on different levels
Mingyao is still young
She can take her time to learn
I do need to learn
But I'm used to learning while checking evidence
Fu's is on a higher level
Surely logic wouldn't be replaced by seniority
You speak quite sharply Mingyao
I'm used to it
Trained in the Su family
Honed at times when evidence
wasn't believed
Later I found explanations are useless
Only evidence works
Someone who could on her wedding day
decisively switch the groom
shouldn't have bad judgment
Heh
Mr Fu is right
My judgment is indeed not bad
At least I picked a great groom